Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Reference Service Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Public Services records, 2016-2017; Accession 2018-A-007
  - Reference Correspondence
    - BER-BIS, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - BLA-BOW, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - BOY-BROO, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - BRU-BUH, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - BUK-BY, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - CAB-CAR, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - CAS-CHU, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - CER-COO, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - COR-CUT, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - DA-DEM, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - DEN-DER, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - DES-DUR, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - E, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - F-FIR, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - FIT-FUN, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - G-GH, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - GI-GO, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - GR-GUT, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - HA-HAM, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HAN-HAZ, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - HE-HER, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - HES-HIX, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HO-HOU, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - HOV-HY, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - I, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - ILL (A-NJR), 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - ILL (OKS-ZYU), 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - J, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - K-KEL, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - KEN-KI, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - KL-KO, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - KR-KW, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - L-LAS, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - LAU-LEN, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - LES-LIM, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - LIN, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - LIP-LOW, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - LOZ-LY, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - M-MAP, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - MAR-MAY, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - MB-McD, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - McE-McS, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - ME-MIG, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - MIL-MIY, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - MOD-MOS, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - MU-MY, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - N-NEW, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - NG-NUG, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - O, 2016-2017 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - P-PEE, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - PEL-PEZ, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - PH-POI, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - POL-PUT, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Q, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - R-RAN, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - RAO-RES, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - REY-RIE, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - RIG-ROM, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - ROS-RY, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - S-SA, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - SC-SCHN, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - SCHO-SC, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - SE-SHA, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - SHE-SIN, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - SIR-SON, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - SOR-STI, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - STO-SZ, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - T-TH, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - TI-TZ, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - U, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - V, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - W-WAR, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - WAS-WES, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - WH-WIG, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - WIL, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - WIN-WY, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - X-Y, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Z, 2016-2017 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Access Agreements: MS 1090, 2016-2017 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    General
    No other access agreements for FY 2016-2017.
  - Reprographics Order Forms
    - A-BER, 2016-2017 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - BEV-C, 2016-2017 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - D-F, 2016-2017 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - G-H, 2016-2017 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      No "I" order forms for fiscal year 2016-2017.
    - J-L, 2016-2017 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - M-N, 2016-2017 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - O-Q, 2016-2017 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - R-SM, 2016-2017 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - SN-V, 2016-2017 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - W-Z, 2016-2017 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Loan Documentation, 2016-2017 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Vendor Services, Various, 2016-2017 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Reference email (computer files), 2006-2012; Accession 2017-A-0063 (Box 1)
  - [no label information], 2017-A-063-0001; 1 (Box 1)
- Public Services records, 2017-2018; Accession 2019-A-0009
  - Reference Correspondence, 2017-2018
    - A-AL (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - AM-AP (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - AR-AY (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - B-BAN (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - BAR-BAX (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - BEA-BEN (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - BER-BI (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - BL-BOQ (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - BOR-BOY (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - BRA-BRI (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - BRO-BRY (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - BU-BY (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - C-CA (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - CE-CHI (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - CHO-COL (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - COM-COV (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - CR-CU (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - D-DEN (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - DER-DI (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - DO-DU (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - E-EL (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - EM-EZ (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - F-FI (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - FL-FU (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - G-GE (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - GI-GOO (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - GOR-GRE (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - GRI-GU (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - H-HAP (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - HAR-HAY (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - HE-HI (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - HO-HOP (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - HOR-HY (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - I (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - ILL (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - J (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - K-KA (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - HE-KH (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - KI-KN (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - KO (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - KR-KW (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - L-LEP (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - LER-LIM (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - LIN-LY (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - M-MAN (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - MAR-MAY (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - MC (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - ME (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - MI (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - MO-MY (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - N-NE (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - NG-NY (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - O-OL (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - ON-OZ (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - PA (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - PE (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - PH-POP (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - POR-PU (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Q-RA (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - RE-RI (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - RO (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - RU-RY (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - SA (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - SC (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - SE-SI (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - SK-SO (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - SP-STO (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - STR-SY (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - T-TH (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - TI-TU (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - U-V (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - WA (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - WE (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - WH-WI (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - WO-WY (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Y (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Z (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Reprographics Order Forms, 2017-2018
    - A-BE (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - BO-BU (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - C (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - D-F (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - G (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - H-J (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - K (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - L (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - MA-MC (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - ME-N (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - O (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - P (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - R (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - S (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - T-V (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - W (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Y-Z (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Tax Exemption Forms, 2017-2018 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Loan Documentation, 2017-2018 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Vendor Services, Various, 2017-2018 (Box 5, Folder 97)